# Liam Neufeld

Bachelor of Arts & Science in Interactive Systems Design @liam.neufeld@sasktel.net (306) 716-8679 Saskatoon, SK

Recent University of Saskatchewan graduate with a bachelor's in interactive design. Driven, creative, and dedicated professional individual with superb problem-solving and decision-making abilities. Excited to start career, sharpen skills, and gain experience.

### Education

Bachelor of Arts and Science in Interactive Systems Design

University of Saskatchewan

09/2017 - 06/2023 Minor: Psychology Certificate: Computing

### Work Experience

### Service Team Member

Saskatoon Soccer Centre Inc.

10/2021 - 03/2023

- Interact with guests in a friendly manner and maintained Centres and fields for guest activities.
- Supervised centres independently.
- Trained new employees.
- Set up and maintained facilities' scheduling program, which hundreds of guests used to find games.
- Former Henk Ruys Centre Captain.

#### Line Cook

Brown's Social House (Lawson Heights)

05/2021 - 08/2021

- Responsible for preparation and accuracy of meals.
- Maintained a steady workflow in a fast-paced environment.
- Organized and prioritized daily tasks to meet deadlines.

### Line Cook / Delivery Driver

Haywood's Grill

05/2017 - 02/2021

- Grew from dishwasher to line cook.
- Responsible for preparation and accuracy of meals.
- Operated kitchen independently.

### Volunteer Experience

## Volunteer Lead - Game Development Workshop

Digitized

05/2023

- Guided students to workshops around campus.
- Assisted workshop leader with Unity course setup on lab computers.
- Helped answer and direct questions from dozens of students during workshop.

### **Projects**

### Android Studio Geocache App

- Worked alongside a team of 4 other students to design and implement a geocache database app.
- Utilized Android Studio and Google Maps API to create app.
- Acted as Scrum Lead and Head UI Programmer.

### Tyranny of the Feline

- Worked alongside a team of 10 other students to create a small boss-fight arena game.
- Practiced Agile development methodologies.
- Utilized Unity and Aseprite to create game
- Acted as lead character and UI artist